The film on this site's front page cost
$8.26 to produce, logged line for line,
and I can document every cent.
Here's the problem with most portfolios.
You have to take their word for it.
A nice reel, big claims, no receipts.
This site works differently.
It runs like a newsroom. Every claim links
to a source. Every illustration says how
it was made, and the systems that made them
are public. Take the flagship,
PictureLock. Step one: you hand it a plain
text script. Step two: it generates the
narration, the score, the sound design,
the shots, the captions, even a Spanish
dub. Incluso un doblaje al español.
Step three: it logs every call,
model, and cost to a run manifest and prints
the receipt. That's how a 53-second film
lands at $8.26, and the same gates that
checked it check this whole site.
Voice scoring, code review,
resolution audits, public,
dated, zero open flags. Even this voice
is synthetic, cloned from me with my consent.
I'm Mitchell. If you're hiring for AI production
work, there's a 12-minute path from start
to verdict. So look around,
check the receipts, and when you're ready,
come find me.